sportsrageous.com 2013-05-21

# Privacy | Sportsrageous

### Privacy

What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how Sportsrageous.com (“Sportsrageous.com”) treats information which personally identifies you (personal information) that Sportsrageous.com collects and receives. The personal information we collect may include your name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. Once you provide Sportsrageous.com with personal information, you are not anonymous to us. 

There are several links from the Sportsrageous.com site to third party information and service providers who may collect personal information from you in order to provide you with information or services. Sportsrageous.com has no control over the privacy policy of any third party company, so please examine their privacy policy prior to submitting any personal information. This privacy policy only applies to the Sportsrageous.com web site. 

Information Collection and Use

General:  
When you read stories at Sportsrageous.com, Sportsrageous.com does not collect any personal information from you. 

Sportsrageous.com collects personal information when you submit feedback or enter a contest. We may also receive personal information from you, for example when you: respond to an email requesting feedback.

When you visit Sportsrageous.com pages, we may collect certain information about your visit from your browser, including the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet, the date and time you access the Sportsrageous.com site, the pages that you access while at the Sportsrageous.com site and the Internet address  
of the site from which you linked directly to the Sportsrageous.com site. Sportsrageous.com aggregates non-specific visitor information for statistical purposes, such as which stories are most popular, and which stories are read more frequently. 

This information is used to help improve the Sportsrageous.com site, analyze trends, and administer the site. 

Sportsrageous.com uses your personal information for the following general purposes: to determine a winner to contests, to respond to your feedback and to alert you of winners to a contest you’ve entered. In addition, we use your information to send out our weekly newsletter.

Sportsrageous.com uses aggregate and non-personal information to conduct research and to provide reports for Sportsrageous.com business partners and customers. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure

Sportsrageous.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

You elect to receive information from contest sponsors by checking the “opt in” box for that contest. Sportsrageous.com will share your personal information only as you have elected. 

Advertisements served by third party Internet advertising technology companies, appear on pages throughout the Sportsrageous.com site.

Some advertisements may request personal information directly from you or take you to web sites that may request your personal information. Sportsrageous.com has no control over its advertisers’ privacy policies, so please examine the privacy policy of any company advertising on the Sportsrageous.com site prior to submitting any personal information. In addition, some ad-serving companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser and may use information  
about your visits to the Sportsrageous.com site and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Please be aware that when you provide personal information to Sportsrageous.com and authorize Sportsrageous.com to share the information with a third party, your personal information becomes the property of Sportsrageous.com and/or the third party.

Sportsrageous.com and/or the third party may use your personal information to process your request and provide valuable services. Sportsrageous.com will only share your personal information with third parties under a confidentiality agreement or similar arrangement that restricts the third party from sharing your personal information with others. 

If you do not want your information to be used for marketing by or a third party, do not “opt in” or agree to such use when you provide your personal information through the Sportsrageous.com site. If you do not want your non-specific information used for marketing please do not submit your information through our contests.

Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use  
information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information. 

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may also transfer personal information about you if Sportsrageous.com is acquired by or merged with another company. 

Based on client activity or on information that has been provided, Sportsrageous.com may display targeted advertisements on the Sportsrageous.com site, but Sportsrageous.com does not provide your personal information to the advertiser in order to display the targeted ads. Sportsrageous.com and third-party advertising companies note some of the pages you visit through the use of pixel tags. Sportsrageous.com and third-party advertising companies (which  
may include network advertisers) may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about  
goods and services of apparent interest to you. The information collected by third-party advertising companies through the use of these pixel tags is not personally identifiable. 

Sportsrageous.com site content is also integrated into other web sites. These web sites may collect personal information from their visitors that may or may not be used in conjunction with the Sportsrageous.com site content. Prior to supplying any personal information to any third party company linking to Sportsrageous.com site, please read and understand their privacy policy. 

Cookies

Sportsrageous.com lets other companies, including business partners and companies that show advertisements on some of our pages, set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. 

Advertisers or other companies may have access to Sportsrageous.com’s cookies. You have the ability to accept or  
decline these cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other web sites you visit. 

Protection of Minor’s Personal Information

Sportsrageous.com is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from minors. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Sportsrageous.com may occasionally update this privacy policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top of the privacy policy. If we make such changes to this privacy policy, we will place a prominent notice at the top of the privacy policy and you will also see the word “Updated” next to the Privacy Policy link on the front page of the Sportsrageous.com site. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to stay informed about how we  
are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and any up-dates.

Posted by: Coach Fabulous on November 4, 2010   
Filed under:
